iseeme.com 2019-11-12

# Privacy Policy

I See Me! LLC is committed to respecting your privacy and recognizing your need for appropriate protection and management of contact information you share with us. (The phrase "contact information" means any information by which you can be contacted or personally identified, such as your name, mailing address, email address, telephone number, etc.). The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to inform you what information we may collect from you, how we use such information, and the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to review, correct and opt out of our use of, the information. This Privacy Policy applies to information we collect about you through our websites and mobile applications and over the phone. By using any of our websites, mobile applications, or sharing your contact information with us, you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

As a part of our commitment to your privacy, I See Me! LLC supports and adheres to the guidelines and practices adopted by the Direct Marketing Association's Privacy Promise to American Consumers. We have agreed to (1) provide customers with notice of their ability to opt out of information rental, sale, or exchange with other marketers; (2) honor customers' requests not to share their contact information with other marketers; and (3) honor customers' requests not to receive mail, telephone, or other solicitations from I See Me! LLC.

## COLLECTING INFORMATION ABOUT YOU

There may be times (such as when you purchase or order a product, subscribe to a service, register to receive catalogs, or to participate in contests, sweepstakes or promotions, etc.) when we ask you to provide certain contact information about yourself, such as your name, shipping/billing address, telephone number, email address, social media user name, credit card information, birth date, gender, occupation, personal interests, and other information. We may also maintain a record of your product purchases. Whether or not to provide such information is completely your own choice. But if you choose not to provide the information we request, you may be unable to purchase products, or access certain services, offers and content on our websites. In addition, we may need to contact you via phone, email or mail to address questions or issues specific to your order, entry, etc., even if you have opted to not receive marketing communications from us.

We may track the Internet domain address from which people visit us, other electronic markers and identifiers and other information about our site and mobile app traffic. We may analyze this data for preferences, trends, site usage statistics and to recognize you. We may also receive usage data from your mobile phone or other device you use to access our websites or our mobile applications, including location data, which we may also combine with other information.

If you access any of our websites or mobile applications with your log-in credentials from a social networking site (e.g., Facebook or Twitter) or if you otherwise agree to associate your account with us with a social networking site, we may receive personal information about you from such social networking site, in accordance with the terms of use and privacy policy of the social networking site. We may add this information to the information we have already collected from you via our stores, websites and mobile applications.

## USING INFORMATION ABOUT YOU

We use your contact information for analytical and marketing purposes, such as:

  * confirming and tracking your order, subscription, or registration;
  * analyzing preferences, trends, and statistics;
  * informing you of our new products, services, and offers; and
  * providing you with other information from and about I See Me!

We contact you only in ways compatible with your communications choices. To the extent necessary for such purposes, we take reasonable steps to make sure that your contact information is accurate, complete, current, and otherwise reliable.

From time to time we might establish a business relationship with other persons or entities whom we believe trustworthy and whom we have asked to confirm that their privacy policies are consistent with ours. These are known as our Select Partners. In such cases we might rent, exchange, share and/or cross-reference information, including contact information about you that will enable such persons or entities to contact you regarding products and services that may be of interest to you.

To serve you better, we may combine information you give us online, over the phone or through our catalogs. We may also combine that information with publicly available information and information we receive from or cross-reference with our Select Partners and others, including providers of third-party cookie and other third party browsing and use data. We use that combined information to enhance and personalize the shopping experience of you and others with us, and to recognize our customers so that we can communicate with you directly about our products and events that may be of interest to you, and for other promotional purposes.

We may contract with companies or persons to provide certain services including credit card processing, shipping, data analysis and management, promotional services, etc. We call them our Service Providers. We provide our Service Providers with the information needed for them to perform these services. We also ask our Service Providers to confirm that their privacy practices are consistent with ours.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain information when you visit our websites. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third-party web beacon to collect this information. Our systems do not recognize "Do Not Track" signals, but several of these third-party companies who utilize these cookies or beacons on our websites enable you to opt out of this behavioral advertising. To learn more or opt out from these companies you can visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/.

We may share contact information and other data with businesses controlling, controlled by, or under common control with I See Me! LLC.

In certain instances we may disclose your contact information when we have reason to believe that it is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against persons or entities who may be causing injury to you, to I See Me! LLC or to others. We may also disclose your contact information when we believe the law or legal process requires it.

## OPTING OUT OF MARKETING AND TRANSFERS; UPDATING AND DELETING INFORMATION ABOUT YOU

We want to communicate with you only if you want to hear from us. If you prefer not to receive direct marketing from us or from our Select Partners, or if you would like to opt out of our rental or exchange of your information with other marketers, please let us know. In the U.S., you can call us at 877.744.3210 or send us an email at customerservice@iseeme.com. Outside of the U.S., you can send us an email at customerservice@iseeme.com. Please be sure to include your full name, email address, mailing address, and specifically what information you do not want to receive. If you would like to update or correct your email address, mailing address or other contact information with us please contact us the same way. If you like, you may use one of the following statements in your message to us:

  * I prefer not to receive email advertisements, such as updates regarding products and services, special promotions or upcoming events.
  * I prefer not to receive direct mail advertisements, such as periodic catalogs and mailings regarding products and services, special promotions or upcoming events.
  * I prefer not to have my contact information provided to third parties for their marketing purposes.

You may also click the designated link at the bottom of all email advertisements to be removed from future email updates.

Please note that any requests to remove or update your contact information may take up to five days for your email request and 6–8 weeks to process your postal mail request.

## COOKIES

When you visit our websites, we send one or more cookies to your computer or other device. We may also use cookies in emails that you receive from us. A cookie is a small data file that is placed on the hard drive of your computer when you visit a website. A session cookie expires immediately when you end your session (i.e., close your browser). A persistent cookie stores information on the hard drive so when you end your session and return to the same website at a later date, the cookie information is still available. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service when you visit our website and other websites of interest to you. We also use cookies to remind us of who you are, tailor our products, services and advertising to suit the personal interests of you and others, estimate our audience size, assist our online merchants to track visits to and sales at our websites and to process your order, track your status in our promotions, contests and sweepstakes, and/or analyze your visiting patterns.

Certain of our Service Provides may use cookies and collect information on our behalf. In addition, we or certain of our Service Providers, in connection with the services that they provide to us, may provide ads to our customers on our behalf via the Internet or send direct mail or catalogs to customers whom we think may be interested in our products or services. In order to do so, such vendor may collect anonymous information about your visits to our website using a cookie. Third-party vendors may then pool the anonymous information that they collect from our website with other sources of information, which may include your name and mailing address, for purposes of determining whether you might be interested in receiving direct mail or a catalog. If you would like to opt out of accepting cookies altogether, you can generally set your browser to not accept cookies or to notify you when you are sent a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. However, certain features of our websites or other services may not work if you delete or disable cookies.

## SECURITY

We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect the confidentiality and security of information transmitted to us. To guard your information delivered to us electronically, our websites use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL). SSL encrypts your credit card number, name and address so only we are able to decode your information. Unfortunately, however, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your contact information, to the extent permitted by law, we do not guarantee or warrant the security of any information you transmit to or from our websites, and you do so at your own risk.

We urge you to keep any password that you establish with us in a safe place and not to divulge it to anyone. Also remember to log off your account and close your browser window when you have finished your visit. This is to ensure that others cannot access your account, especially if you are sharing a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place.

## PROTECTING CHILDREN

I See Me! LLC takes special care to protect the safety and privacy of children. When you enter personalized information about your child such as your child’s name, gender, birthdate or address, we do not share that information with third parties.

Our websites are general audience sites. We do not permit anyone under the age of 13 to register with us. We also do not send email correspondence to anyone who tells us that they are under the age of 13.

Children under the age of 13 should always ask their parents or guardians for permission before providing any contact information to anyone online. We urge parents and guardians to participate in their children's online activities and use parental control or other web filtering technology to supervise children's access to the Internet.

California users under the age of 18 may request the removal of their content or information publicly posted on websites or mobile applications by sending us an email at customerservice@iseeme.com. Please note that most of the user content that appears on our Site or Services is stored and controlled by third party providers; thus, complete and comprehensive removal of the content may not be possible.

## LINKS TO THIRD PARTY WEBSITES

Our websites may contain links to websites operated and maintained by third parties, over which we have no control. Privacy policies on such linked websites may be different from our privacy policy. You access such linked websites at your own risk. You should always read the privacy policy of a linked website before disclosing any of your information on such website.

## POLICY CHANGES

If we decide to change our privacy policy in whole or in part, we will inform you by posting a notice on our websites, as applicable. Those changes will go into effect on the effective date posted in the notice and at the end of the revised Privacy Policy. The new policy will apply to all current and past users of our websites and will replace any prior policies that are inconsistent. Your continued use of our websites or other services constitutes your acceptance of the practices described in the revised Privacy Policy.

## YOUR FEEDBACK

To help us improve our privacy policy and practice, please give us your feedback. In the U.S., you can call us at 877.744.3210 or send us an email at customerservice@iseeme.com. Outside of the U.S., you can send us an email at customerservice@iseeme.com.

Effective Date: January 24, 2019
